Anasha Maxwell

Personal

Address: #34 Upper Fairley Street, Tunapuna

Email Address: anashamaxwell@yahoo.com

Contact Number: (868) 390-7931

Objective

To enhance and share my acquired knowledge and understanding, and gain experience in the world of work so that I may be able to apply my knowledge meaningfully, contributing not only to my general progress but also to the improvement of organization to which I am attached.

Education

2008-2007

St. Augustine Senior Comprehensive school 2007-2004

Five Rivers Junior Secondary 2004-2001

Good Sheppard Anglican School 2001-1994

Academic Achievements

Mathematics	General	CXC	3
Principle of Account	General	CXC	3
Principle of Business	General	CXC	3
Human and Social Biology	General	CXC	3

Achievements

Beauty Therapy Youth Training and Employment Partnership Programme

(YTEPP) February 2014- July 2014

Microsoft Office Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) 2009-2010

Nail Technician Beauty Technique (Mrs. Malisa Singh) May 2009-April 2009

Hobbies

Steel Pan and Hiking.

Experiences

Southern Caribbean Manufacturers Ltd Inventory Clerk 2014-2011

Corner El Socorro Road & Girez Lane, San Juan

Albrosco Ltd

139A-141B Belmont Circular Rd,

Belmont. Merchandiser/Promoter 2011-2010

Prices Supermarket

327 Eastern main Rd 2010-2007

El Dorado Cashier

References

Dr. Emanuel Hosein MB.Bs Affisha St Louis

Medical Physician Accounts Clerk

Eastern Main Road, Tunapuna Southern Caribbean

Manufacturers LTD

(868) 645-2672/620-4057

(868) 346-0129